Guide to the War Effort Mobilization Campaigns Poster Collection, 1942-1945 RL.01342
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- War Effort Sample Posters Series, 1942-1945, 2 boxes
  - War Manpower Commission
    - Design No. 12, Whistle, 1944 (Box 5)
    - Design No. 12, Whistle, Sales Kit, 1944 (Box 5)
    - Unnumbered Design, Uncle Sam, circa 1944 (Box 5)